<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>grep -r on gr455.github.io/blog</title><link>https://gr455.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in grep -r on gr455.github.io/blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:24:22 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gr455.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Attending the Open Source Summit EU 2022</title><link>https://gr455.github.io/blog/post/oss_eu_2022/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2022 18:24:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://gr455.github.io/blog/post/oss_eu_2022/</guid><description>I have been involved with Open Source for the past 3 years and this September, I got to attend the Open Source Summit in Dublin. This was the first time I attended OSS (or any international conference for that matter) and the experience was unparalleled.
This blog briefs my experience at the Open Source Summit, and contains a bunch of pictures from there
I had applied to the scholarship in the beginning of July and got the acceptance by end of July.</description></item><item><title>GSoC '21 Testbench Project: Final Report</title><link>https://gr455.github.io/blog/post/gsoc_final/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 18:24:22 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://gr455.github.io/blog/post/gsoc_final/</guid><description>This blog post is a report of all my work done on the Testbench Project as a part of GSoC 2021 at CircuitVerse
About the Project CircuitVerse is a Digital Logic Simulator on web. It is an educational tool for students interested in electronics to simulate and make circuits on their browser.
My project is to implement a testbench to automatically test circuits against test cases. This will replace the existing testbench element in favor of more robust testbench which runs faster, supports sequential circuits and gives the user greater control over running tests.</description></item></channel></rss>